All right, go ahead.
>> After after sleeping on last night, um
what's kind of the biggest thing that
jumped out about why things didn't go
your way?
>> Well, similar to how I felt coming off
the field, you know, we had five
possessions on offense inside the 32
yard line and no points and and so for
that to happen, you know, that was
really on pace to be a a 20 to 17 type
of game typically when we play those
guys. And to come away with no points,
that's obviously a big indicator why we
were 24 to nothing. injury-wise, how did
y'all come out of yesterday?
>> We'll see. I I think there's nobody I'm
ready to say um can't go right now. We
had a bunch of guys that kind of got
nicked up and will be limited throughout
the week, but nobody I'd say with
extreme confidence can't go on Sunday.
Maybe as the week progresses, we'll get
there, but not right now.
>> Chris Jenkins, like as I think
>> the oldest guys, I I'd say, you know,
the guys that that come up on the injury
report are going to be Chris Jenkins,
Joseph Osai, um Mims, Noah Fant,
Charlie. Um those those are the main
ones that strike me right now. But
again, I'm not I'm not we'll keep
working through the week and see where
those guys end up.
>> How close was Shamar to playing? And
could he be a possibility again this
week?
>> I think he's a possibility. We we'll
just work through the week and see where
he ends up. Um his first week back at
practice coming off the injury as a
rookie. Um he pushed himself pretty
good. Didn't feel it was the right time
to to put him back in the game. So we'll
work through Wednesday, Thursday, Friday
and see where he lands on that. Now that
you guys are officially out of playoff
contention, will you be more
conservative with deciding on if players
can or can't go?
>> We'll see. Is a that's a case by case
basis to see where everybody ends up.
>> Is it your expectation that Burrow will
start the rest of the season?
>> Yes.
>> You're not going to use it at an as an
excuse, but how much do you feel like
the cold impacted things, especially
offensively yesterday?
>> Well, I think both teams played in the
cold, so certainly won't use that as an
excuse. Um, those are rare temperatures
that was very similar to that New
England game we played in in 22. That's
that's ex identical how it felt. But
again, they they went out there and
played football just like we did. They
coached just like we did and and they
came away with a 24 to nothing win.
>> Has it been any consideration at all to
kind of sit burrow down for the last
three games? Is that did that come up at
all?
>> No.
>> Why not?
>> Because we want to win. What are the
conversations with Joe or what will they
be like after he took so much
responsibility yesterday, Zach, for what
happened? Are you going to break down
the film more closely? Are you going to
have more generic conversations with
them?
>> Well, I don't we break down the film
pretty thoroughly um with all these guys
and I think it's good to see your
leaders take ownership for their
performance. That's that's critical for
us to continue to progress is guys
taking accountability for it. And so I
was I was proud that Joe did that. um
that wasn't his best game he's played
since he's been here certainly and and
for whatever reason that was the cold or
whatever um doesn't really matter at
this point and so again I thought it was
good he took accountability in front of
the team last night um took
accountability in here took
accountability with me I take
accountability I I played a big part in
that as well and so um I think it's good
to see when when your leaders do that
and um I'm not surprised that he did
that that's that's who he is
>> when Joe got hurt a question we asked
you we asked Joe was will he change the
way he plays coming back from the injury
and I think through three games it's a
it's a pretty clear no. What are the
things you like just about his
willingness to extend plays to to take
those type of chances and and what gives
you confidence for him to keep doing
that?
>> Well, there's not really a quarterback
you're going to find in the AFC that
plays in the meaningful games late in
the season that doesn't take those
chances and so to take to take a
superpower away from him where he has
been strong through contact and extended
plays and created big plays from that
stuff. Um, now certainly we want him
healthy throughout the the the season
and his career. And so there is that
balance there of all of that, but when
you watch guys that I don't have to
mention my name that that play on
through the playoffs, a big huge part of
what they do is make plays out of
nothing. And and so again, Joe's done a
great job of that over the course of his
career. And there's just a balance of
staying healthy and also finding the
moment where you can extend those plays
and make those big plays.
>> How much of that depends on him in terms
of being healthy? How much of that
depends on him being able to take care
of himself during a game?
>> It's all of it. I mean, it's again, it's
play calling, it's protection, it's him
decision- making. I mean, that that all
factors into it.
>> You talked about accountability and kind
of in your role and kind of when things
don't go well. What does that
necessarily look like throughout the
course of the week? Uh, I know you tell,
you know, you talk to us about it, but
what does that look like for you in
terms of
>> just with coaches, with players?
Anything where I feel like I've fallen
short and can do better, I'm I'm not
going to hesitate to admit that. Um, I'm
not gonna ask the players to take
ownership for something that that we're
holding them accountable for and I'm not
going to do the same thing. So, I don't
I don't think that's
um I feel very comfortable doing that
and and exposing myself that way, you
know, with him. It's um I don't want
anybody having an ego about this that
it's everybody else's fault. It's not
it's 100% on me, you know, to to be with
the record we're at right now to score
no points yesterday on offense when I
called the plays. That's I I mean um
that starts and ends with me really. And
so we we can talk about all the other
things that happened, but um it's it's
frustrating and and um yeah, it's
disappointing.
>> Building off of that and and yesterday
you said that you were surprised with
how this season has turned. Uh what are
tangible steps that you and your
coaching staff can take in the next
couple months? Well, I I do nobody wants
to hear it, but I do think there's
things on defense that have really
improved, particularly since the buy. Um
there were some opportunities, you know,
yesterday. I think the the really only
two disappointing
primary disappoint, you know, we had a
third down where they scored points on
it where we'd been really effective in
that situation. Um and then at the end
of the half, they got some points there.
But there was a lot of great moments
from the defense yesterday getting off
the field on third down. Um getting
pressure on Lamar, you know, the four
sacks, creating a turnover after we turn
the ball over. And so there are there
are some things that they're improving
on that we're going to continue to build
off of that. So I I think that's
tangible that's showing up. Anybody
who's watching the game can see that
that's improvement being made and
there's a lot of young players that are
participating in that. Second, third
year players that are showing growth
through the season. Um I feel like
obviously yesterday on offense wasn't
wasn't even close to any standard we've
created for ourselves. Uh but there's
been a lot of positives on offense the
weeks leading up to that. And so, um,
I'm not just going to dismiss yesterday
as dismissed yesterday as a one-off
situation. We we have to be accountable
for that. You can't get shut out at home
and walk away and say that's that's not
like us. We're going to be better for
it. We got to make sure that that never
happens again because that that cannot
happen. That can't happen in front of
our fans. Can't happen for our guys in
the locker room. It's unacceptable for
us. But, um, I do expect this week for
our guys to respond the right way to
show we just face some pretty extreme
adversity with with what happened to us
yesterday and how these guys are going
to respond, the coaches and players. Um,
I feel very confident in how we're going
to respond, but we got to go prove that.
>> Is your message with ownership and the
front office the same with them as it is
[snorts] us and the fans?
>> Um, yeah. I just I don't think it's far
off. Um, I have all those conversations
weekly with everybody. Again, like I
said, I'm pretty open with how I feel
about things.
>> What would you say to uh, you know, the
areas you have improved on defense, what
would you what would you say? I
>> I think the experience a lot of these
guys have gotten, they've gotten a lot
of playing time. They they made mistakes
earlier. Those mistakes are starting to
disappear. Um, we're getting pressure on
the quarterback and really affecting the
game that way. Maybe a lot more so than
we did, I think, leading up to the buy.
That's really happening. Um,
There's still some tackling issues that
came up yesterday where we've got to
improve, but I think as a wholesale when
you look at the the scope of the game,
um guys have done a much better job in
that area. So, I think the energy is
good. The the discipline's been really
good. Um they're starting to play
through this scheme the last couple
weeks. They've gotten a ton of
experience in it. All these guys playing
collectively together and they've
responded the right way and and uh
raising their standard of play over
there. And yesterday obviously we just
we didn't match it on offense.
>> When you went through this in 2019 and
2020, was there something that you
learned back then that's helping you
with perspective now when you go through
a season like that?
>> Yeah, certainly. I I think from a
personality standpoint, you know, a lot
of people when things get um things
aren't great, they want you to change
who you are and your personality. And
I'm that's one thing I refuse to do.
That's that's kind of why I'm here today
is because of all the things I've all
the challenges I faced in my life. And
um you know, I'm fortunate. I I learned
from the best in the world. I've learned
from my dad, you know, and that's that's
somebody I know everybody that looks up
to in my life looks up to him. And so um
I've I've learned because you you play
for other coaches and you're on other
teams where maybe the personalities can
change depending on the situation. And
I've never felt that's a great way for
me to lead. So 2019, 2020, um did
everything I could to stay true to who I
was so that the players know what
they're going to get every single day
and what the expectations going to be.
doesn't mean they're all going to be
easy conversations or lack of hard
conversations, but they know what
they're going to get when they get face
to face with me every day. And so that's
not going to change for me in 2025 or
going into 2026. Um, but again, it's I
am disappointed where we are in the
season right now. I feel everyone's
frustration. I feel the same frustration
and we want to finish the season on a
really strong note. That's important to
me. That should be important to
everybody. And we're in this business to
win football games and we haven't won
enough football games and it's very
important we go out and win, you know,
starting this week, you know, forget
about the last two, but um going down to
Miami and putting our best foot forward.
>> Understanding that on the whole the
passing games been great this season.
Looking at the last three games, do you
want to use that to to tinker or explore
some different things, some different
ideas you can try out offensively?
>> There's a balance there certainly, but
number one, we just want to win. And so
without diving into Miami yet and really
knowing much of what they're about
defensively, um which we'll do starting
when I walk out of here, but uh the most
important thing is finding a way to win
this game and and creating that positive
energy for our guys in the locker room
and for our coaching staff and everyone
associated with this. And so um that
takes the priority over over anything.
any any personnel question, any scheme
question. Um, that's a fair question
because there are things that you you
want to maybe take a peek at and see if
you can be better at, but but the number
one priority will be what do we have to
do to win this game and be successful
that way? And anything else will be
secondary to that.
>> Whether it's now or, you know, earlier
in the year or in the offseason, how
much do you think about how the results
affect how you're viewed and kind of
your performance?
>> That that has no bearing on me
whatsoever. Um, when I tell you there's
a a brick wall surrounding me and
isolating me from any feelings people
have about me or their views on me, I
can't allow that to dictate how I
operate. And so, um, truthfully, I I
that doesn't affect me in any way,
shape, or form. And I just keep doing my
job to the best of my abilities, and um,
this year certainly hasn't been good
enough with the record we're at right
now. I I get that. Um, but I'm just
going to keep doing everything I can to
get this team ready to play on Sunday.
inside that wall and kind of how you
view yourself. How do you do you think
about that at all? I mean, at any point
over the course of the year, offseason,
inseason, late season, how much do you
think about that?
>> I just look at anything I can control to
make this team better. That that's all I
can try to analyze. How you put that
into words is difficult. I've certainly
got through a myriad of things. I I try
to follow to make sure every facet of
this program is is functioning as high
as it needs to. Um but but it's
difficult for me to sit up here and put
into words on how I do all that. wait
until the end of the year to
self-evaluate.
>> No, I do that every week. No, I mean
that's honestly since since early part
of the season. I try to reflect on every
week and every game, every schedule on
things I would change, things I do
differently, things I learned from. So,
I think to wait till the end of the
season. Obviously, there's more big
picture things after the season that
you'll you'll focus on with everybody,
but not there yet. But again, I I take
time every single week um to make sure
that I've got my thoughts in order so
when you get to the end of the season,
you're not trying to reflect back and
remember anything you would change or
anything you did differently. I I lose
sight of all that. So, I got to do it as
I go.
>> How important are the final three games
of this season for the culture of the
locker room and momentum going into the
offseason?
>> Well, I I I just want to take it one
game at a time. I don't want to focus on
all three. And that's what I told our
guys. We've got a lot of obviously um
frustration on our end because we
haven't played up to the standard that
we believe we we should be held
accountable to and so you get an
opportunity on Sunday to go down there
and and show the world how we're going
to handle adversity and that's that's
all we're going to focus on this week.
>> Is there a nonquest but you know you
talked about diving in Miami after this.
Does it kind of change the approach or
does it maybe give you an advantage
with, you know, them playing a team a
game tonight and they're playing against
a division opponent like you being able
to watch that live to start the
preparation?
>> Um, watching it live doesn't do much
because we we have access to that during
the week. So, we watch the live games
all all the time to make sure we're
trying to hear communication and
anything that's said that way. Um,
certainly them them playing on a shorter
week is um that's you're not going to
sugar coat that. That's an advantage for
us to have seven days as opposed to them
having six.
>> Is there anything in hindsight that you
wish you would have done differently in
the off season that maybe could have put
you in a better position at this point?
>> It's hard to put my finger on that
because I I felt good coming into the
season that that was going to happen. I
don't want to make an excuse for
anything that happened during the season
that set us back. It is you got to every
team in this league has faced some form
of adversity and some have found ways to
work through it and find wins. Um, we
had a lot of games that were right
there, could go either way. And and more
times than not, we did not find the win.
So, um, I don't have one particular
thing that I can pinpoint that I would
do differently in the offseason.
Obviously, kind of kind of to the
question earlier, you go into this
offseason, you're going to look at
everything to make sure, um, you can
make any change you can. Last offseason
was about starting faster and and
changing everything and we started 2
and0 and here we are with four wins here
in December. previous years we've been
outstanding in December and January and
[snorts] um that hasn't been the case
right now. Zack, uh, and this might be
kind of a casualty to the week- toeek
approach that you're staying in, but I
just wonder if with the defensive
progress if
that has any of if that looks like a
kind of foundational
progress that
you can build on that could carry over
from year to year. it you you look at uh
players in specifically, you look at
position groups, you look at the unit as
a whole and which which direction are
they moving and and I think they're
moving in a positive direction. So I
think it's simple as that. Um obviously
we want to get to a point where where we
expect the team to not score on any
drive and we're creating a lot of
turnovers and putting pressure on the
quarterback and that we're right now
we're just we're moving in a positive
direction. it it's uh I don't like
saying that right now because you just
lost a game the way we lost it and our
record is what it is and I don't think
anybody really wants to hear that but um
I do feel I do feel that they were they
were trending in a positive direction
>> outside of the game uh yesterday there
were a lot of fans that were upset and
frustrated about the snow situation in
their seats there's any message to them
>> I don't I I appreciate the people that
came out I mean really it was that's
that's like I said tied for the coldest
game I've ever been in in my entire life
and it it takes a lot to sit through
that and and for us to perform like we
did um is frustrating and so the people
that did come out and fought the
conditions it's much appreciated and we
have to show better for that.
>> Ask about T. How's he going through
protocol?
>> He's still in the protocol so I don't
have much comment beyond that.
>> Okay. Thank you.